
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <channel>
   <title>The Lazy Blog</title>
   <link>https://karanmitroo.github.io/</link>
   <description>Recent content on The Lazy Blog</description>
   <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 17:52:26 +0530</lastBuildDate>
   
       <atom:link href="https://karanmitroo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
   
     <item>
       <title>__init__</title>
       <link>https://karanmitroo.github.io/posts/init/</link>
       <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 17:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
       
       <guid>https://karanmitroo.github.io/posts/init/</guid>
       <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello World!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After procastinating for more than an year now, I have finally set my blog up. This time I chose to use github pages for hosting the content as compared to deploying my own wordpress server which I did alomst 2 years back. This static site is built using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gohugoio/hugo&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;. I recently came to know about Hugo and since it has been written in Go I started exploring it. But spending time exploring it was yet another excuse of not setting up the blog. So I have planned to explore it side by side as I setup the blog and push some content. The good thing about hugo is that I will be writing all my posts in Markdown. Which gives me the freedom to switch to any other framework if required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-am-i-writing-a-blog&#34;&gt;Why am I writing a blog?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned before, this is the second time I have started to write a blog. The major reason to write a blog is to make myself read more. This sounds weird right?! Let me explain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I used to write my first blog back in 2018, I made some observations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, to write something I would have to read someting. So this puts me in a habit of exploring/ reading new content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And because this blog is going to be present on the Internet I will have to put some efforts in understanding what I am going to write about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thus all in all it helps me keep myself up to date in this fast moving world of Tech.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-will-i-be-writing-about&#34;&gt;What will I be writing about?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am glad you asked! Majorly, the posts are going to be about Tech. &lt;strong&gt;Software Development&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Reliability&lt;/strong&gt;  are the two things I will be focussing on initially. As that is what I am into at the moment. But at the same time I would also post some random blogs here and there around anything interesting that I come across.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;thats-it-for-this-blog-&#34;&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it for this blog 😄&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;really-excited-to-have-completed-my-blogs-setup-lets-wait-for-some-interesting-content-in-the-coming-few-days-&#34;&gt;Really excited to have completed my blog&amp;rsquo;s setup. Let&amp;rsquo;s wait for some interesting content in the coming few days 🤘&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
     </item>
   
 </channel>
</rss>
